Andrea Fan

Proactive, creative and a proven team player with 5 years experience in marketing and customer successs. Curious about how to build a product and wish to be part of it.

I am seeking a entry-level frontend developer job to begin my developer career and my goal is to be able to contribute company and community.

shan32157@gmail.com	>
+886 975-766-257	

linkedin.com/in/andrea-fan-b98491b9/

github.com/AndreaFan123

WORK EXPERIENCE

Codapayments

Senior Marketing

12 / 2020 - 12 / 2022 Taipei, TW

- Achieved significant revenue growth in Taiwan as measured by recording daily, monthly revenue. Achieved 2 million USD revenue in July.
- Accomplished a co-brand campaign and achieved 15% revenue growth as measured by revenue growth rate, by subtracting previous monthly revenue and multiplying 100.
- Established content and social media strategy by collaborating with different FB groups and freelancers, blog pageview grew from 0% to 5% per month.
- Executed social media Esport campaigns, achieved 90% satisfaction as measured by questionnaire.

Elex Technology

Community Manager

06 / 2019 - 12 / 2020 Taipei, TW

- Managed FB fan page with 3 million fans and established social media and campaigns.
- Organized player gathering, achieved 100% satisfaction, measured by questionnaire.
- Initiated CSR project in 2019 Protect Taiwan's Leopard Cat with local kindergarten.

Wargaming.Net

Sales Optimization (Team Lead)

05 / 2018 - 02 / 2019 | Singapore

- Increased 10% revenue by implementing culture-fit in-game customisations and bundles.
- Increased 5 10% engagement by leveraging trending topics and memes
- Organized player gathering, achieved 99% satisfaction, measured by questionnaire.

Customer Service Specialist

12 / 2017 - 05 / 2018 Taipei, TW

- Participated in projects, including CS website revamption, user experience analysis and building knowledge base.
- Identified and implemented customer success strategy and collaborated with other functions to improve customer satisfaction.

Ministry of Defense

Chief Counselor

09 / 2010 - 04 / 2015 | TW

SKILLS

HTML Influence Marketing

CSS3 Social Media Marketing

JavaScript Content Marketing

React Event Planning

Firebase Google Analytics

python

MySQL

Flask

Figma

CERTIFICATION

UI / UX Specialisation

Certification

Certificated By CAL ARTS

EDUCATION

WeHelp Coding Bootcamp

Web Trainee

12 / 2021 - 07 / 2022 Taipei, TW

- Accomplished a frontend multi project management web application.
 - https://glance-simple-work-space.web.app/
 - https://github.com/AndreaFan123/glance
- Accomplished a full stack travel application.
 - http://52.194.56.157:3000
 - https://github.com/AndreaFan123/taipei-day-trip-website

Tamkang University

Bachelor of Arts (B.A.) of Russian Language and Literature

12 / 2021 - 07 / 2022 | Taipei, TW



English

OTHER
Confluence

